So with lazy loading added, we finished the optimization of our project. Feel free to do more, to organize
Po dodaniu leniwego adowania zakoczylimy optymalizacj naszego projektu. Moesz zrobi wicej, uporzdkowa foldery w
your folders differently or outsource more functions into a helper functions.
inny sposb lub zleci dodatkowe funkcje w funkcje pomocnicze.
I think we have a nicely optimized well working application which looks good, which behaves exactly as
Myl, e mamy adnie zoptymalizowan, dobrze dziaajc aplikacj, ktra wyglda dobrze, zachowuje si dokadnie tak, jak
it should behave,
powinna si zachowywa,
also on mobile devices and which allows us to really present a pleasant user experience to the user
take na urzdzeniach mobilnych i ktra pozwala nam naprawd zaprezentowa uytkownikowi przyjemne wraenia uytkownika i korzysta
and use a lot of the features react gives us.
z wielu funkcji, jakie daje nam reakcja. .
Now in the next modules, we'll fine tune this application to be ready for deployment,
Teraz, w kolejnych moduach, dostroimy t aplikacj, aby bya gotowa do wdroenia.
with that I actually mostly mean I'll show you how you could test the application automatically.
Zasadniczo mam na myli, e poka ci, jak moesz automatycznie przetestowa aplikacj.
Then we will deploy it and then we will have a totally finished react application.
Nastpnie wdroymy go, a nastpnie otrzymamy cakowicie gotow aplikacj reagowania.
So let's move on.
Przejdmy dalej.